>> Brian Holt: 我希望您现在创建一个名为 carouse.js的新文件。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I want you to go make
a new file now called carousel.js.
>> 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 所以你想做一个漂亮的卡鲁索
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
you want to make like a nice Carousel so
人们就喜欢看动物的各种照片，对吧 ?
that people can like see the various
different pictures of the animals, right?.
首先我们要做的就是把 " 反应 " 从 " 反应 " 中
So first thing we're gonna do here is
we're gonna say import React from 'react'.
>> Brian Holt: 然后我们会说类 Carousel 扩展了 React.Component。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then we're gonna say
class Carousel extends React.Component.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，这会有两个我们要做的事情
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so
this is gonna have two things we're gonna
有一系列的各种不同的图像
have an array of all the various
different images, and
我们现在要展示的是活跃的活跃指数
we're gonna have which one we're currently
showing, the active one, the active index.
所以我们会说国家的照片照片会是一个活跃的阵列
So we're gonna say state =, and
the photos is gonna be an active array,
活动将会是一个数字。
and active is going to be a number.
因此，我们将在缺省情况下选择第一个。
So we're gonna by default
select the first one.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，然后我们继续
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, and
then let's go ahead and
渲染渲染， >> Brian Holt: 因此
make the render,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
当我说合拍照片
when I say const photos and
active = stats 状态和
active = the stats state and
我们要回到一个
we are going to return a div
类名 = carousel。
class name = carousel.
>> Brian Holt: Carousel 是一个词，我越说越觉得奇怪，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Carousel is a word that
the more I type the more it looks strange,
我不知道我不明白我不明白
I just can't,
don't know I don't understand it.
然后我们就会把你的照片和照片
Then we are gonna put and image and
这个来源会和照片一样活跃对吧
the source is gonna be equal to photos,
active, right?
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特( Brian Holt) : 所以，照片很活跃，这将会是一系列照片，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So, photos active,
this is gonna be an array of photos and
我选的第二个就是两个对吧
stuff I select the second one,
that will be two, right?
我来选那个
And I'll select that one.
然后，这里的备用文本将会被放置在动物或类似的东西上。
And then, the alt text here will put for
it is animal or something like that.
>> Brian Holt: 然后，我们将输入类名 = carousel- 更小。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then we are gonna
put do class name = carousel- smaller.
> > Brian Holt: 接下来我们将把
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
then here inside of that we are gonna put
photos.map ， >> Brian Holt: And
photos.map,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
然后映射有两个它提供的参数。
then map has two parameters
that it provides.
其中一个是照片吧
One of them is the photo, right?
但它也给了你一个第二个指数。
But it also gives you a second
one that is the index.
所以当你抓住那个指数的时候， >> Brian Holt:
So when you grab that index as well,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
然后我们就会在这里做个暗示
then we're gonna do
an implicit return here.
>> Brian Holt: 如果我们更加关注越好
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: If we were
being more attentive to better
可访问性实践在这里。
accessibility practice is here.
也许我们要做的就是做这个小按钮对吧
Probably what we'll do is to
make this little button, right?
比如看到我们点击更小的按钮
Like to see we'll click on
the smaller buttons and
这会导致这里的互动
that would cause an interaction over here.
用于处理焦点的 Cutz 按钮
Cuz buttons handle focus a lot better for
只是时间上的问题不在生产上
just the sake of time don't
do this in production but
我要让你直接把事件收听者直接放在图像上
I'm gonna show you just to put the event
listener directly on the image.
>> 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
the key is gonna be the photo.
>> Brian Holt: 然后单击要对其执行某些操作的 onClick 。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then onClick where
gonna have to do something with that.
所以我们要说 " handleIndexClick"
So we're gonna say this.handleIndexClick,
我们将在这里短暂地建造
which we will build here momentarily.
>> Brian Holt: 当您为其提供数据索引时，以及我们要执行的操作
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: When you give it the data-
index, and what we're gonna do with
如果有人单击该按钮，那么会在此处而不是句柄索引中单击。
this is here instead of the handle index
click if someone clicks on the button,
然后我们就把索引从这里的图像中提取出去
then we're going to pull
the index off of the image here.
这是源 equals photo className =。
This is source equals photo className =.
因此，如果索引是 triple = 活动的，那么我们想给它一个活动的类。
So, if the index is triple = to the active
then we want to give it an active class.
要不我们就不去上课了，
Otherwise we don't wanna
give it a class okay,
然后它就会成为动物的缩略图
and then the alt is going
to be animal thumbnail.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，这会说你做了一件坏事
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, and this is gonna say
you did a really bad thing just belong
具有快速句柄的交互开发必须至少有一个键盘侦听器。
interact developments with quick handle
must have at least one keyboard listener.
>> Brian Holt: 在这里，你可以做一些类似的事情。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
here you can do something like on.
>> Brian Holt: 在关键操作或类似的操作上，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: On key op or
something like that,
就像处理那样的事情
equals handle something like that.
我们现在不会这么做的
We're not gonna do that right now.
现在我们要忽略这一点
For now, we're just going to ignore this.
> > Brian Holt: 我很愿意教人们你能做到这一点，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I like hesitate to
teach people that you can do this,
就像你可以忽略任何东西
it's like you can ignore anything,
这些都是我的核心工作对你很不高兴
cuz one of these is eventually gonna be my
core work and am gonna be so upset at you.
>> Brian Holt: 我过去做过，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I went through and
did this correctly and
得花很多时间才能在这方面获得正确的信息，所以现在
it takes a lot of time to get the
accessibility correct on this, so for now
我想让你做正确的工作但我们现在就要开始行动了
I'm admonishing you to do it correctly,
but we're just gonna move on for now.
>> Brian Holt: 好，现在我们必须进行该句柄 indexClick。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so now we have
to go make this handle indexClick.
让我们先做个出口，因为我总是忘了这个。
Let's go ahead and just do the export at
the bottom because I always forget this.
因此，导出，缺省值， carousel，类似
So export, default, carousel, like so
现在我们要去做个 " indexClick" 了
and then now we're gonna go
make the handle indexClick.
好吧，让我们先说吧，这是个有趣的游戏。
Well, let's do the derive state
first this is kind of a fun one.
照片会从父组件传递到轮播
So the photos are gonna be passed in from
the parent component into the carousel
所以它不会在细节页里提出要求
ride, so it's not gonna get request in the
details page, it's gonna request that, and
然后我们就会把它塞到车里了对吧
then we're going to set that
here in carousel, right?
但这副会给我们一个大物体
But the pair is gonna give us a large
object full of lots of photos in
各种大小的，其实就是想除草。
various different sizes and
they actually just want to weed out.
这就是我们需要的大小。
So just the sizes that we need.
我要展示如何使用静态的 getDerivedStateFromProps，
So, I'm gonna show you how to use
static getDerivedStateFromProps,
我要把媒体拿掉
I'm gonna grab media out of this, so
这是一种特殊的反应方法，它必须是静止的，好的。
this is a special react method
that it must be static, okay.
它要做的是在一组道具中
And what it's gonna do is,
it's gonna take in a set of props and
给你一个新的国家
give you back a new set of states.
所以我要说让照片
So I'm gonna say let photos
相当于另一个位置相关图片的新数组。
equals new array full of another
place correlate picture.
就像这样 corgey.com/600x600
Place corgey.com/600x600 like that.
因此，如果它没有任何图像，那么这将是缺省图像，好吗 ?
So this would be the default image
if it doesn't have any images, okay?
否则，如果是 media.length，
Otherwise, if media.length,
然后我想让你说照片
then I want you to say
photos = media.map and
我要把所有的大照片都拿出来
I'm just gonna pull out
all the large photos.
>> Brian Holt: Large 并返回。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Large and return that.
>> Brian Holt: 对，这些照片对象将具有小，中，大和
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Right, so these photo
objects will have small, medium, large and
我们只是抓住他们的照片
full, and we're just grabbing
the large photos out of them.
所以现在照片就是一系列的 URL ，好吗 ?
So now photos will just be
an array of strings of URLs, okay?
然后我们就会把我们想要的东西
Then down here we're going to return
whatever object that we want to be merged
进入了国家
into the state.
我们会说回来的照片
So we're gonna say return photos.
>> Brian Holt: 因此， getDerivedStateFromProps 再次发生
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So, again,
getDerivedStateFromProps takes in a set
属性，对其进行过滤，然后将其传递到组件。
of properties, does some filtering on them
and then passes that on to the component.
所以这个组件根本不会看到媒体的道具。
So this component's actually
never gonna see the media props.
永远都不会用的对吧
It's never really gonna use them, right?
会用这种照片来保持状态
It's gonna use this photos
which is gonna keep in state.
因此，如果您有任何派生的状态，那么这是处理这些情况的好方法。
So if you have any derived state, this is
a good way to handle those situations.
你不必这么做的
You don't have to do it this way.
我完全可以在这里说而不是照片的地图
I totally could have come down here and
said, instead of photos dot map,
我就会说这个停停的计划
I would have said this
stop props.media.map.
然后我就会把照片里的照片和照片都给我
And then here I'll set photo.large and
photo.large.
如果你觉得这是个好主意我就把它留给你
I'll leave it to you decide if you
think this is a good idea or not,
我喜欢它是因为它把一些逻辑抽象化成了这种处理程序
I like it because it abstracts out some
of the logic into this kind of handler,
但是 > > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
but
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Up to you.